linkinpark.com 2008-12-16

# LINKIN PARK / PRIVACY POLICY

## Privacy Policy

### Introduction

Clique (“Clique”), a business unit of Sparkart Group, Inc., cares deeply about your privacy and the protection of your personal information, which is why we have devised this Privacy Policy. This policy statement describes how Clique helps protect your personal information. By using the Clique Services, you consent to the data practices described in this policy statement. Defined terms designated in the Terms of Use shall have the same definitions in this Privacy Policy.

### Collection of Personal Information

When you register for the Clique Services, you will be asked to provide certain personal information that will be stored as part of your registration data. The registration data contains various personal information which may include, but not be limited to, the following: (1) e-mail address, (2) first and last name, (3) country or region, (4) state or territory, (5) city, (6) zip code or postal code, (7) street address, (8) time zone, (9) gender, (10) language, (11) birth date and age, and (12) occupation. In addition to the above information, Clique may also collect and store the IP address of your computer or other networking device, which may be needed to operate various features of the Clique Services. We may also collect data pertaining to your online transactions, purchase history, and Clique Site and Clique Services usage patterns. Further, when you register for the Clique Services, you may be asked to create a password for your account. You may also be requested to provide secret questions and secret answers. You use your secret questions and answers, if applicable, to help verify your identity to Clique when there are account issues, such as needing to reset your password. You may also be requested to answer various questions about your consumer preferences or other information. Finally, we and some participating sites may require added security. In these cases, you may be asked to create a Clique ID security key.

### Use of Your Personal Information

#### How We Will **Not** Use Your Personal Information:

  * Except as stated in the next sentence, Clique will not sell or rent your personal information to third parties. Clique may sell, rent and disclose your personal information to the following third parties: artists and organizations for whom we operate a Web site (for example, a music group for whom we are operating a fan club Web site), and artists and organizations for whom we are selling concert tickets or merchandise. Please be aware that these third parties may have their own policies governing how they will use and disclose your personal information which may be different from this Privacy Policy.
  * Clique will not use or share your personal information in a manner that differs from what is described in this Privacy Policy without your prior consent.

Clique uses your personal information for the operation and maintenance of your Clique account and the Clique Services. For example, we may use your e-mail address to send you a welcome e-mail message when you first register informing you about the service and telling you how to manage your Clique account. You may be required to respond to this e-mail in order to validate that you are the owner of the email address associated with the Clique account. If applicable, failure to respond to the email and verify the address within the time stated in the email will cause the Clique account to become inactive. This process is designed to verify the validity of the email address and to help prevent email addresses from being used without permission in the creation of Clique accounts.

As part of the Clique Services, we may recommend for your consideration various products and merchandise. Accordingly, we may analyze data pertaining to your online transactions, purchase history, and Clique Site and Clique Services usage patterns so that we can make recommendations suited especially to you.

We may also send you e-mail about periodic service or recommended security updates or surveys related to the Clique Service. These periodic e-mails are considered essential to the provision of the service you have requested. You cannot unsubscribe from these mailings. You may, however, choose not to participate in the surveys.

### General Disclosure of Personal Information

Clique occasionally hires other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, such as answering customer support inquiries. Clique will only provide these companies with those pieces of your personal information needed to deliver the services, and the companies and their employees are prohibited from using that personal information for any other purpose.

Clique may share your personal information with third parties in order to fulfill a service or transaction you may have requested.

Clique may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process served on Clique; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Clique; or (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of the Clique Service, or the public.

### Disclosure of Personal Information to Clique ID Participating Sites

The information about you stored in the Clique ID system is not shared with a Clique ID participating site, service or system unless you explicitly choose to use your Clique ID to register or sign in with the participating site. When you use your Clique ID to register or sign in with the participating site, service or system, the participating site, will receive some or all of the information about you stored in the Clique ID system. It is important for you to read the privacy statement for each Clique ID participating site, service or system that you visit before you register or sign in, so that you understand how that site may use your personal Clique ID information. Also, if you registered for a Clique ID through a participating site, service or system, then that registering site will receive the profile information at the time of registration.

### Use of Information by Clique ID Participating Sites

Clique ID participating sites, services and systems with whom you choose to share the information can use it for a variety of purposes. These can include personalizing your experience at their sites and reducing registration time by using information in your Clique ID account to pre-fill their registration forms. Clique ID participating sites and services may share your personal information with third parties in order to fulfill a service or transaction you may have requested. In addition, participating sites may share your personal information with third parties as permitted by their own privacy policies.

To become a Clique ID participating site or service, the operator must agree to have a posted privacy policy and to use commercially reasonable efforts to comply with industry-standard privacy guidelines and practices. Nevertheless, we do not control or monitor the privacy practices of Clique ID participating sites, services or systems and the privacy practices of those sites will vary. You should carefully review the privacy statement for each Clique ID participating site you sign in to in order to determine how each site or service will use the information it collects.

If Clique becomes aware of ongoing, site-specific privacy issues with a Clique ID participating site, service or system, we will work to address those issues with the site. If at any time you believe that a Clique ID participating site has not adhered to these principles, please notify Clique by e-mail.

### Managing Your Personal Information

You can always add, update, or make other changes to the registration information stored in relation to your Clique ID. This is accessible by signing in to any Clique ID site in which you are registered. If you have a Clique ID, you may close your Clique ID account by contacting [Clique Customer Service](mailto:customersupport@cliqueinc.com).

### Sharing Your Personal Information

If you choose, you may opt-in to various features which may be available as part of the Clique Services which allow the voluntary sharing of information between you and a group of Clique users designated by you; for example, a “buddy list” or “friends” who also have a Clique ID.

### Security and Storage of Your Personal Information

Clique is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. For example, we store the personal information you provide on computer systems with limited access, that are located in controlled facilities.

You must type the correct password to access your information. It is your responsibility to ensure the security of your Clique account password and not to reveal this information to others.

Personal information collected by Clique may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which Clique or its affiliates, subsidiaries, or agents maintain facilities. By using the Clique Service, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country.

### Operational Information

Some “operational” information is used by Clique in order to operate your account properly and provide the Clique Services. This operational information does not include the personal information that you provide as part of your Clique registration data, but may include, for example, the following: the date on which your registration data was last updated, whether your e-mail address has been verified, whether your account has been deactivated, what browser you are using, the IP address of your computer or other networking device, and other similar types of information. Operational information may be shared with third parties to the extent necessary to provide Clique Services.

### Aggregate Information

We may collect and analyze information about your use of the Clique Services as aggregated with the use of the Clique Services by other users (“Aggregate Information”); for example, overall usage patterns of Clique users, the total number of Clique users, the percentage of Clique users who are female, or in a certain age range, or who live in a particular region, etc., or the percentage of Clique users who are also consumers of various other products and services. The collection and analysis of Aggregate Information is important in the operation and enhancement of the Clique Services and other business purposes. Aggregate Information may be compiled in reports and disclosed, sold, licensed or rented to third parties. However, since Aggregate Information does not include any information which can be used to individually identify you or any other Clique user, it is not possible for the third party recipient of the Aggregate Information to use it to identify or contact you.

### Use of Cookies

A cookie is a very small text file that a Web site saves to your computer’s hard disk to store information that you provide about yourself or to store your preferences. The Clique Services may use cookies when you sign in to or access a Clique Web site. The Clique Services store your unique identifier, the time you signed in, and Clique registration data in an encrypted cookie on your hard disk. The cookie allows you to move from page to page at the participating site without having to sign in again on each page.

The Clique Services may also use cookies to improve the sign in experience. For example, the Clique Services may store your user name in a cookie that will remain on your computer after you sign out. This cookie allows your user name to be entered automatically, so that you will only need to type your password the next time you sign in.

You may have the ability to accept or decline cookies using the settings on your browser. However, if you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to sign in or use the Clique Services.

### Change to This Privacy Policy

Clique may occasionally update this Privacy Policy. When we do, Clique will endeavor to provide notice to users in the following ways: (1) Clique will update the “last updated” date at the bottom of the Privacy Policy; (2) Clique will post notice of the change as a news post on the Clique Site; and (3) Clique may email notice of the change to all Registered Users. Clique will obtain your consent for any updates to this Privacy Policy that expand the sharing or use of your personal information in ways not disclosed in this Privacy Policy.

### Contact Us

If you have questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact [Clique Customer Service](mailto:customersupport@cliqueinc.com).

**Last Updated: December 4, 2007**
